insta-stalker.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy

We are grateful to you for visiting us that here referred to as insta-stalker.com or the site. Before you use the site, make sure to read this privacy policy. If you don't agree with privacy policy document, please don't use the site. By accessing or using the site, you expressly consent to our storage, collection, use and disclosure of your personal information.

The privacy of our users is important for us. We help you to understand how we use, collect, store and disclose your data.

You are free to surf the insta-stalker.com without revealing any personal data making it possible to identify you. But you have submit your identifiable personal information to us once, no longer you are anonymous to us. We collect two types of data: “Automatic Anonymous Information” and “Identifiable Personal Information”.

**AAI (Automatic Anonymous Information)**

The site automatically monitor your certain information depending on your behavior. This information does not identify you personally. To improve the site and It's functionality, we use this information that include your IP address, the browser you use and other informations. This information is referred to here in as the AAI.

**IPI (Identifiable Personal Information)**

IPI is independently identifiable data about you that enables us to distinguish or reach you. Our contact form require asking you for certain IPI for example your full name, e-mail address as well as other individual data. You can always choose not to provide this information.

**Content Rights**

We don't store and host any of the Instagram user data on this website, all rights belong to their respective owners.

**Sharing of Information**

The site will target advertising in light of individual data gave by clients and induced from site utilization. This may include age, gender or geographic information. The site does not give any individual data to the promoter when you connect with or see a focused on advertisement. Notwithstanding, by interfacing with or seeing a promotion you are consenting to the likelihood that the promoter will make the suspicion that you meet the focusing on criteria used to show the advertisement. We may package and offer the non-individual data we gather from you and different clients with promoters, outsiders, trusted accomplices and members so they show advertising that better suits your interests.

We might be required by law authorization, government managers, as well as legal experts to give actually identifiable data. We will unveil by and by identifiable endless supply of a court arrange, or if required to co-work with law implementation, regulatory or other legislative offices. We maintain whatever authority is needed to answer to law implementation organizations any exercises that We in accordance with some basic honesty accept to be unlawful.

**Cookies**

We use cookies to collect non-personal information. It helps us for smooth user experience, remember you on future visits, better understand how users engage with the site so we can enhance the user experience. The use of these cookies is optional and you can configure on your browser not to accept or to only sometimes accept.

**Links**

On insta-stalker.com you will find various external links directing you to Third Party Sites or Third Party Content. The site not be liable for the links posted by users or the privacy policies of such third parties.

**Changing of Our Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is liable to change at whenever. You should to occasionally review and check this so you generally will comprehend what data we gather, with whom we share it and how we utilize it.

**Contact**

For any inquiries concerning this Privacy Policy, different arrangements for the site, how to utilize the site, please get in touch with us.
